desert-operations.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy

The takes the protection of your personal data very seriously and strictly adheres to the rules of data protection laws. Personal data on this website are only needed for technical purposes. On no account the raised data will be sold or otherwise shared with third parties.

The following declaration gives you an overview of how guarantee this protection and what kind of data are raised for what purpose.

## Personal data

Personal data are information communicated by you, that can be used to find out more about yourself and your identity. Personal information are information such as your name(s), address, postal address, telephone number. The information that is not associated in a direct way to your true identity, such as links and statistic, - internal data are not included.

Basically, the offers of can be used without disclosing your identity. If you are interested in one of our personalized services and register or order one of our products, we will ask you about your name and other personal information.

Your personal information will be stored on servers which are located in Germany. The administrative access to these servers is done by a small number of persons who work either for technical, commercial or editorial issues.

In connection with your access to our servers some data will be stored for security purposes, which may allow identification (eg IP address, date, time and pages viewed). There is no exploitation of personal data. The statistical analysis of anonymous data is reserved.

We save IP addresses over a period of 28 days. The storage is done for reasons of security in order to ensure the stability and reliability of our system.

As far as the provide its own online forums for use by third parties, they receive no access to the stored personal data of the forum users. Their management is the sole responsibility of the .

## Disclosure of personal information to third parties

We use your personal information in the case of product orders only within the and affiliated companies. We do not refer them without your express permission. If, in case of data processing, data should be referred to service provider, so they are bound to the BDSG, other statutory provisions and contractual the Privacy Policy of too. As far as we are required by law or court order to refer your data, we will refer your data only to the relevant authorities.

Posts in our discussion forums and comments are accessible to everyone. You should carefully check your posts before publishing, so that they do not contain any information, you do not want to make public. You must expect that your posts were garhered by search engines and get accessible worldwide even without a specific request of our offer. The deletion or correction of such entries from foreign operators often cannot be enforced.

## Cookies

Internet pages use so called cookies in several places. They serve to make our offer more user-friendly, effective and safer. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer and stored by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies". Cookies do not do harm to your computer and do not contain viruses.

## Newsletter

For the receipt of newsletters we need a valid email address and information that allow us to verify that you are the owner of the e-mail address respectively the owner agrees the receipt of the newsletter. You are able to revoke your consent for storing the data, the e-mail address as well as their use for sending the newsletter at any time.

## Children

Persons under 18 years should not convey any personal data to us without the consent of parents or legal guardians.

## Links to other websites

Our online portal containes links to other websites. We have no influence on whether the operator of these websites observes data protection regulations.

## Access Right

You have the right to obtain information about your personal data, its origin and recipient and the purpose of storage. Our data protection supervisor will give you information about the stored data via email to [info(at)looki.com](mailto:info@looki.com).

## More information

Your trust is important to us. Therefore we will always justify ourselves to you concerning the processing of your personal data. If you have any questions, you are not answered by this privacy policy, or if you want more in-depth information, please contact our data protection supervisor at any time via mail to [info(at)looki.com](mailto:info@looki.com).

## Personal Data

To delete your personal data, please contact our data protection officer via email to [info(at)looki.com](mailto:info@looki.com).
